http://www.hillnews.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
TRENDING:
Biden transition
Joe Biden
Donald Trump
Coronavirus
SPONSORED:
Global Lenses UAE
Privacy Policy
THE HILL'S PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) is applicable to The Hill's Web site (thehill.com), The Hill app, and any other Hill websites (collectively “The Hill” or the “Site”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and share information from you and other users of the Site.Information We CollectWe collect information in multiple ways, including when you provide information directly to us and when we passively collect information from or about you, such as from your browser or device. We may combine all of the information we collect from or about you from these various sources. Information You Provide Directly to Us We collect any information that you provide to us, including, but not limited to, during the following interactions: (1) when you register on the Site and when you log-on with your user name and password; (2) when you sign-up to subscribe to a service, a newsletter, or ask to be added to our mailing lists for other products or services; (3) when you place an order for products or services; (4) when you participate in a promotional offer; (5) when you provide feedback in an online survey; and (6) when you submit other content and suggestions.In each of the instances above, we typically ask for some or all of the following information:Contact information, such as your full name, e-mail address, phone number, and physical mailing address,Business information, such as the type of business you are in,Request information, such as product preference information,Authentication information, including any applicable identification number or password that we may require,Payment information, such as credit card number (which goes through our payment processors--we do not store such information)other similar information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers.On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain other information, materials and services. Information We Collect Through Automated Means We also collect information through automated and technical means as you browse or use the Site. Usage Information. As you browse the Site, we and our service providers (which are third party companies that work on our behalf to provide and enhance the Site) use a variety of technologies, including cookies and similar tools, to assist in collecting information about how you interact with the Site. For example, our servers automatically record certain information in server logs. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, domain name and settings, referring / exit pages and URLs, how you interact with links on the Site, pages viewed, mobile carrier, mobile device identifiers and information about the device you are using to access the Site and other such information. Location Information. We collect and process general information about the location of the device from which you are accessing the Site (e.g., precise or approximate geographic location inferred from an IP address). Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. We and our service providers may also collect data about your use of the Site through Internet server logs and online tracking technologies, like cookies and/or tracking pixels. A web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you visit a website that enables us to: (a) recognize your computer; (b) understand the web pages of the Services you have visited; (c) recognize repeat users; (d) facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of a website (e) allow the Site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising; (f) enhance your user experience by delivering content and advertisements specific to your inferred interests; (g) perform searches and analytics; and (h) assist with security administrative functions. Tracking pixels (sometimes referred to as web beacons or clear GIFs) are tiny electronic tags with a unique identifier embedded in websites, online ads and/or email, and that are designed to provide usage information like ad impressions or clicks, measure popularity of the Site and associated advertising, and to access user cookies. We and our service providers may also include Web beacons in email messages, newsletters and other electronic communications to determine whether the message has been opened and for other analytics, personalization and advertising. As we and our service providers adopt additional technologies, we may also gather additional information through other methods.  You can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., Internet Explorer; Google Chrome; Mozilla Firefox; or Apple Safari). However, note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain Site features or offerings. How We Use the Information Collected We may use the information we collect from and about you for the following purposes: For the purposes for which you provided it;To maintain, provide, and improve the Sites;To enhance your experience at the Site and, where applicable, as a subscriber to The Hill’s products and services;To prevent or address technical or security issues;To send you information or other communications, such as newsletters (with your consent, when applicable);To process and respond to your inquiries or to request your feedback;To identify you by your device(s) and to match your device(s) with other browsers or devices you use for the purpose of providing relevant and easier access to content and other operational purposes;To engage in internal analytics, research, and reporting;To comply with the law and protect the safety, rights, property, or security of the Site and the general public; andTo enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Site.The Hill may merge your information collected on the Site from or about you (including automatically collected information) with information we obtain about you from our affiliates, subsidiaries, and/or non-affiliated third parties, and use such combined information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.We may aggregate and/or de-identify information collected through the Site. We may use aggregate/de-identified information for any purpose, including without limitation for research and analytics, and may also share such data with any third parties, including partners, affiliates, subsidiaries, services providers, and others. Sharing with Third Parties We may disclose and/or share your information under the following circumstances: Affiliates and Subsidiaries. We may share the information we collect within The Hill family of companies. Service Providers. We may provide access to or share your information with select entities that use the information only to perform services on our behalf. These service providers provide a variety of services to us, including without limitation, processing of transactions, provision of content and features, administering of promotions, sweepstakes, surveys, providing marketing or promotional assistance or similar such services, analytics, data storage, security, fraud prevention, and other services. Direct Marketing. We may share the information with third party partners to provide you with information, including marketing, about services that we think you might want. You may at any time opt-out of receiving promotional communications from The Hill or sent by the Hill on behalf of third parties at any time by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at the address below. Please note that if you decide to opt-out of receiving promotional information or other communications after you have previously opted-in, your change in preference will only affect future contacts; if the information already has been provided to third parties, they may continue to use it. We may still contact you as necessary regarding The Hill, any request you have made for services or products from The Hill, changes to this Privacy Policy and other transactional matters. Business Transactions. We may disclose your personal information in connection with the evaluation of or entering into a corporate transaction where all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information) change ownership, are sold, or are transferred. Third Parties for Legal Purposes. We may disclose your information where we determine in good faith that it is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process or a government or regulatory investigation (e.g. a subpoena or court order); (b) enforce our Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, or other contracts with you, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; and/or (d) protect our rights, property or personal safety, or that of our agents and affiliates, our users and/or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for information security, fraud protection, spam/malware prevention, and similar purposes. Online Advertising. We may use your information to facilitate the delivery of targeted ads, promotions, and offers to you, on behalf of ourselves and third party advertisers, on and off the Services.  Third-party networks and advertising technologies allow for the delivery of advertising from our advertising partners on The Hill and about The Hill on other websites you visit. We may share with these third parties (or they may directly collect) data such as cookie and mobile ad identifiers in order to engage in advertising activity (including to understand how you respond to our advertisements). If you are interested in more information about how you can generally limit cookies from being put on your computer to deliver certain types of advertising, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Opt-Out link to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. We do not control these opt-out links or whether any particular company chooses to participate in these opt-out programs. We are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued availability or accuracy of these mechanisms.   Website Analytics and Do-Not-Track Website Analytics. We may use third-party web analytics services on our Site to collect and analyze usage information through cookies and similar tools; engage in auditing, research, or reporting; and provide certain features to you. To prevent Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking here. Notice Concerning Do Not Track. Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information collected on our Site for third party purposes. However, we do not currently recognize or respond to browser-initiated DNT signals. To learn more about Do Not Track, you can do so here.Unaffiliated Third Parties on the SiteIf you voluntarily disclose information in an e-mail or other communication with third parties found on the Site or in other materials, that information, along with any other information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by such third parties and may result in you receiving unsolicited messages from other persons. Such collection, correlation, use and messages are beyond our control.For California ResidentsIf you are a California resident, California law requires us to provide you with some additional information regarding how we collect, use, and share your “personal information” (as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)). Categories of personal information we collect.  Throughout this Policy, we discuss in detail the specific pieces of personal information we collect from and about users.  Under the CCPA, we are also required to provide you with the “categories” of personal information we collect.  The categories we collect are:  identifiers (such as name, address, email address); commercial information (such as transaction data); financial data (such as credit card information); internet or other network or device activity (such as browsing history or Site usage); professional or employment related data (such as information about your type of work); general geolocation information (e.g., your precise or general location, such as your city and state based on IP address or precise location); and other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with you.How we use these categories of personal information.  We and our service providers may use the categories of personal information we collect from and about you for the following business purposes and commercial (as those terms are defined in applicable law):  Our or our service provider’s operational purposes;Auditing consumer interactions on our site (e.g., measuring ad impressions);Detecting, protecting against, and prosecuting security incidents and fraudulent or illegal activity;Bug detection and error reporting;Customizing content that we or our service providers display on the Site (e.g., contextual ads);Providing the Site (e.g., customer service, advertising and marketing, analytics, and communication about the Site);Improving The Hill and developing new services or offerings (e.g., by conducting research to develop new products or features);Other uses that advance our commercial or economic interests, such as third party advertising and communicating with you about relevant offers from third party partners; andOther uses about which we notify you.Examples of these types of uses are discussed throughout this Policy and specifically in the section on Sharing with Third Parties above. We may also use the categories of personal information for compliance with applicable laws and regulations, and we may combine the information we collect (“aggregate”) or remove pieces of information (“de-identify”) to limit or prevent identification of any particular user or device.Categories of personal information we disclose for business purposes We may disclose any of the following categories of information about you or your use of the Site for business purposes (as defined by applicable law) or as required by applicable law:Identifiers (such as name, address, email address); commercial information (such as transaction data); financial data (such as credit card information); internet or other network or device activity (such as browsing history or app usage); professional or employment related data; geolocation information; inference data about you; and other information that identifies or can reasonably associated with you. Notice of Right to Opt Out of Sale of Personal Information California residents may opt out of the “sale” of their personal information. Under the CCPA, sale is broadly defined such that it may include allowing third parties to collect or receive certain information, such as cookies, IP address, and/or browsing behavior, to deliver targeted advertising on the Site or other services.  Advertising, including targeted advertising, enables us to provide you certain content for free and allows us to provide you offers relevant to you. We may provide the following categories of personal information to third parties for these purposes:For online targeted advertising purposes: demographic and statistical information, user-generated content, device information and identifiers, connection and usage data, geolocation, and social media information.Contact and registration information; demographic and statistical information, employment and education data, user-generated content, and geolocation.If you would like to opt out of The Hill’s use of your information for such purposes that are considered a “sale” under California law, you may do by clicking the Do Not Sell My Data in the footer or by submitting a sale opt-out request by emailing us at help@thehill.com.  Please note that we do not knowingly sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age without legally-required affirmative authorization.California Privacy Rights If you are a California resident, you may have certain rights.  California law may permit you to request that we:Provide you the categories of personal information we have collected or disclosed about you in the last twelve months; the categories of sources of such information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling your personal information; and the categories of third parties with whom we shared personal information.Provide access to and/or a copy of certain information we hold about you.Delete certain information we have about you.You may have the right to receive information about the financial incentives that we offer to you (if any). You also have the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising certain of your rights. Certain information may be exempt from such requests under applicable law. For example, we need certain types of information so that we can provide the Site to you and for compliance with applicable law.California customers may request, once per year, that we disclose the identity of any third parties with whom we have shared personal information for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed.If would like to exercise any of these rights, please email us at help@thehill.com. You will be required to verify your identify before we fulfill your request. To do so, you will need to provide your email address. You can also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. To do so, you must provide us with written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.Our Commitment to Data SecurityThe Hill has put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on the Site.  Notwithstanding our commitment to protect your information from loss, misuse or alteration by third parties, we cannot remove all risk associated with transmitting information electronically. Additionally, there also is some risk our security systems could be circumvented or breached. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.Correcting InformationYou are responsible for providing accurate information when making purchases, registering with any portions of the Site that require registration, or performing other functions that might require you to submit information to the Site. If you wish to correct any personally information you have provided to us, then you may do so by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at the address below.How To Contact UsIf you would like to contact The Hill for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write or e-mail us at the following address:Mailing Address:The Hill Information Privacy Manager 1625 K St. NW Suite 900 Washington, DC 20006 e-mail: help@thehill.comChanges To The Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of December 31st, 2019. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We may notify you of changes by posting a notice on the Site or by contacting you through electronic mail or other means. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept those changes.What If You Do Not Agree To The Terms Of This Privacy Policy?As a subscriber to the Site, or otherwise by using the Site, you signify that you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not make any use of the Site.
Most Popular
Video
Aaron Glantz warns of possible 'replay' of 2008 housing crisis in coronavirus financial downturn
Rising
What is the legacy of Pete Buttigieg's historic run as America's first gay presidential candidate?
Changing America
Former Sanders spokesperson: Nina Turner House candidacy 'very exciting prospect' for the left
Rising
You could soon be scrolling Facebook while gazing into the eyes of your dinner companion
Changing America
More From The Web
Sponsored
Don't miss a brief. Sign up for our daily email.
Your Email
News
Senate
House
Campaign
Administration
Regulation
Media
Jobs
The Hill 1625 K Street, NW Suite 900 Washington DC 20006 | 202-628-8500 tel | 202-628-8503 faxThe contents of this site are ©2020 Capitol Hill Publishing Corp., a subsidiary of News Communications, Inc.
